<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on The Ups and Downs of Being a Human</title><link>https://kernpinoy.github.io/post/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on The Ups and Downs of Being a Human</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 23:59:55 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kernpinoy.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>What a Friend</title><link>https://kernpinoy.github.io/p/what-a-friend/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 23:59:55 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://kernpinoy.github.io/p/what-a-friend/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://kernpinoy.github.io/p/what-a-friend/pexels-helena-lopes-1049317.jpg" alt="Featured image of post What a Friend" />&lt;p>Oftentimes, When I find myself in times of trouble (Paul McCartney much?), I just shutdown myself and breakdown.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Like a lot.
&lt;strong>A lot, lot, lot!&lt;/strong> It&amp;rsquo;s been like that for quite some time.
In many instances, I&amp;rsquo;ll just cook ramen and think about things that I know I should, but alas, the mighty intrusive thoughts have won.
Imagine about thinking about how peaceful could it be if you can have the opportunity to unalive yourself, permanently.
Or if somehow if I can get a lot of money, maybe all my problems can be solved!
Or thinking that if I am dead, many of our problems would not exist, causing them to have improved familiar relations with one another.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>You know, the usual stuffs, for me I guess. I know it, the irony is not lost with. That&amp;rsquo;s highy problematic. It really it. Not only it is on borderline sadboyism,
it omit toxic qualities that no one except someone who&amp;rsquo;s crazy would be fucking fine with that! I have now changed, since then.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>It started at my first year of college. They were hesitant to interact, nevertheless, problematic codes have found a way for us to bond. Solving their C and Java codes were not easy, but it was good funthat I have.
That&amp;rsquo;s the catalyst, I think. 2nd year was&amp;hellip; Let&amp;rsquo;s just say the half of it was a shitty experience.
&lt;strong>Especially the 2nd semester.&lt;/strong> I was crying most of the time. While there are many silver linings on that A.Y., that was not enough to mask the bruises.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>During those times, they were there for me. In fucked-up moments and in happy hours, they were there for me.
I can&amp;rsquo;t help but be thankful for them.
They helped me in many things that I cannot say.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This is for them.&lt;/p>
&lt;div class="highlight">&lt;div class="chroma">
&lt;table class="lntable">&lt;tr>&lt;td class="lntd">
&lt;pre tabindex="0" class="chroma">&lt;code>&lt;span class="lnt">1
&lt;/span>&lt;span class="lnt">2
&lt;/span>&lt;span class="lnt">3
&lt;/span>&lt;span class="lnt">4
&lt;/span>&lt;span class="lnt">5
&lt;/span>&lt;span class="lnt">6
&lt;/span>&lt;span class="lnt">7
&lt;/span>&lt;/code>&lt;/pre>&lt;/td>
&lt;td class="lntd">
&lt;pre tabindex="0" class="chroma">&lt;code class="language-c++" data-lang="c++">&lt;span class="line">&lt;span class="cl">&lt;span class="cp">#include&lt;/span> &lt;span class="cpf">&amp;lt;iostream&amp;gt;&lt;/span>&lt;span class="cp">
&lt;/span>&lt;/span>&lt;/span>&lt;span class="line">&lt;span class="cl">&lt;span class="cp">&lt;/span>
&lt;/span>&lt;/span>&lt;span class="line">&lt;span class="cl">&lt;span class="kt">int&lt;/span> &lt;span class="nf">main&lt;/span>&lt;span class="p">(&lt;/span>&lt;span class="kt">int&lt;/span> &lt;span class="n">argc&lt;/span>&lt;span class="p">,&lt;/span> &lt;span class="kt">char&lt;/span>&lt;span class="o">**&lt;/span> &lt;span class="n">argv&lt;/span>&lt;span class="p">)&lt;/span> &lt;span class="p">{&lt;/span>
&lt;/span>&lt;/span>&lt;span class="line">&lt;span class="cl"> &lt;span class="n">std&lt;/span>&lt;span class="o">::&lt;/span>&lt;span class="n">cout&lt;/span> &lt;span class="o">&amp;lt;&amp;lt;&lt;/span> &lt;span class="s">&amp;#34;Thank you, really. I have no words. Thank you.&amp;#34;&lt;/span> &lt;span class="o">&amp;lt;&amp;lt;&lt;/span> &lt;span class="n">std&lt;/span>&lt;span class="o">::&lt;/span>&lt;span class="n">endl&lt;/span>&lt;span class="p">;&lt;/span>
&lt;/span>&lt;/span>&lt;span class="line">&lt;span class="cl">
&lt;/span>&lt;/span>&lt;span class="line">&lt;span class="cl"> &lt;span class="k">return&lt;/span> &lt;span class="mi">0&lt;/span>&lt;span class="p">;&lt;/span>
&lt;/span>&lt;/span>&lt;span class="line">&lt;span class="cl">&lt;span class="p">}&lt;/span>
&lt;/span>&lt;/span>&lt;/code>&lt;/pre>&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>&lt;/table>
&lt;/div>
&lt;/div>&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Note: I am using they/them pronouns to further mask their identities.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote></description></item><item><title>On birthdays and stuffs</title><link>https://kernpinoy.github.io/p/on-birthdays-and-stuffs/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 23:49:43 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://kernpinoy.github.io/p/on-birthdays-and-stuffs/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://kernpinoy.github.io/p/on-birthdays-and-stuffs/pexels-pixabay-33688.jpg" alt="Featured image of post On birthdays and stuffs" />&lt;p>My friends either did not know that my birthday was on the 17th of June or they forgot. I don&amp;rsquo;t blame them for that. Everyone must be busy, that&amp;rsquo;s all. But I don&amp;rsquo;t know, It hurts so much. Even my relatives forgot my birthday - they&amp;rsquo;re the only ones to greet me since I don&amp;rsquo;t have close friends or friends - just acquaintances.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I was really looking forward that someone would greet a happy birthday.
They made me care about birthdays. Because everyone seems to be happy. But it&amp;rsquo;s the same experience. The same ordeal that I&amp;rsquo;ve gone through most of my life.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I know their birthdates. I know them because I care about them. That&amp;rsquo;s why I know them. Because they are dear to my heart. This is my first interaction with the outside world since exiting a cult that robbed me of my childhood. Leaving me slow in comprehending the real world. Because they were busy fencing my life.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>But that&amp;rsquo;s OK, it&amp;rsquo;s just a birthday. They&amp;rsquo;re busy. They have their own life. They have their shit together. I think I&amp;rsquo;m just envious of them. They get greetings all the time.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Anyhoo, that&amp;rsquo;s something I am pondering on.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>What Am I Doing Wrong?</title><link>https://kernpinoy.github.io/p/what-am-i-doing-wrong/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 01:11:46 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://kernpinoy.github.io/p/what-am-i-doing-wrong/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://kernpinoy.github.io/p/what-am-i-doing-wrong/pexels-dorran-1643280.jpg" alt="Featured image of post What Am I Doing Wrong?" />&lt;p>Oftentimes, I find myself desperate for attention, hoping that anyone would notice me.As I recall in my childhood, I&amp;rsquo;ve been pleasing people most of my life.
I will literally do anything in my power not to disappoint anyone. Whether it&amp;rsquo;s some person that wants their laptop check, or helping with their coding problems,
I will go to your place. Not the opposite.
I know, that really sucks but it is what it is. I do not want my friends to be burdened by inconvenience. I guess I have to take it up to my ass.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Let me tell you need to know first. I&amp;rsquo;ve been a part of a cult since my childhood. Most of my &amp;lsquo;friends&amp;rsquo; were the children inside their, which I grew up with, basically.
I did not make connections to the outsiders, indoctrinating me with the belief it is better to be friends with people inside the church than the outsider.
The rationale behind this is that insiders are more trustworthy. As I view this now, this only builds a fence to a child that further isolates, enabling deeper brainwashing.
Having said that, I&amp;rsquo;ve left the cult and was doing pretty fine in the early days. Not anymore. Connecting with friends was great, until it shattered. It killed me since then.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>With the remnants of that friendship, I&amp;rsquo;ve noticed something. I hope I am wrong. Please let me be wrong. I want to be wrong on this observation.
While I trusted them, it seems that they have not done the same. I think nobody really trusted me in the first place.
I mean, they did not even I think I am just being used. I&amp;rsquo;m not smart in any way possible, let&amp;rsquo;s be clear that out.
I&amp;rsquo;m the regular, most basic bitch, and the most annoying person you&amp;rsquo;ll meet in your existence.
I don&amp;rsquo;t know if I&amp;rsquo;m just stressed or whatnot.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Meanwhile, I always remember Slavoj Žižek&amp;rsquo;s interview.&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>I agree with Sophocles: the greatest luck is not to have been born
but, as the joke goes on, very few people succeed in it.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>- Slavoj Žižek&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>I hope to be proven wrong. They&amp;rsquo;re blameless. They&amp;rsquo;re kind to me.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I think that the best course of action is to do nothing. Fuck myself and my life.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>