<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>sadness on The Ups and Downs of Being a Human</title><link>https://kernpinoy.github.io/tags/sadness/</link><description>Recent content in sadness on The Ups and Downs of Being a Human</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 23:49:43 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kernpinoy.github.io/tags/sadness/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>On birthdays and stuffs</title><link>https://kernpinoy.github.io/p/on-birthdays-and-stuffs/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 23:49:43 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://kernpinoy.github.io/p/on-birthdays-and-stuffs/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://kernpinoy.github.io/p/on-birthdays-and-stuffs/pexels-pixabay-33688.jpg" alt="Featured image of post On birthdays and stuffs" />&lt;p>My friends either did not know that my birthday was on the 17th of June or they forgot. I don&amp;rsquo;t blame them for that. Everyone must be busy, that&amp;rsquo;s all. But I don&amp;rsquo;t know, It hurts so much. Even my relatives forgot my birthday - they&amp;rsquo;re the only ones to greet me since I don&amp;rsquo;t have close friends or friends - just acquaintances.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I was really looking forward that someone would greet a happy birthday.
They made me care about birthdays. Because everyone seems to be happy. But it&amp;rsquo;s the same experience. The same ordeal that I&amp;rsquo;ve gone through most of my life.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I know their birthdates. I know them because I care about them. That&amp;rsquo;s why I know them. Because they are dear to my heart. This is my first interaction with the outside world since exiting a cult that robbed me of my childhood. Leaving me slow in comprehending the real world. Because they were busy fencing my life.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>But that&amp;rsquo;s OK, it&amp;rsquo;s just a birthday. They&amp;rsquo;re busy. They have their own life. They have their shit together. I think I&amp;rsquo;m just envious of them. They get greetings all the time.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Anyhoo, that&amp;rsquo;s something I am pondering on.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>